## **Tanner Muldoon**

3000 NW 130th Terrace Apartment 229 Sunrise, FL, 33323 U.S. Citizen

tannermuldoon@gmail.com 404-834-4699

I'm a recent graduate from **Georgia Tech** currently working at **L3Harris Technologies**. I have sizeable personal experience with **real-time software**, both with **embedded RTOSes** and user-facing software such as video games. My main concentration is in **embedded systems engineering**. At my current workplace, I work primarily in **digital signal processing** for **software defined radios**.

#### Education

### Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, GA

Bachelors of Science in Computer Engineering, GPA 3.74

June 2016 — May 2019

- Graduated with Highest Honors
- Minor in Computer Science and Systems & Architecture

# Work Experience

### L3Harris Technologies | Sunrise, FL

Associate, Software Engineering

June 2019 — Present

L3Harris is an aerospace and defense technology company, and a leading provider of tactical radios

- Engineer working on digital signal processing C code for HF radios
- Designed a new PSK modem implementing the HFDL protocol at the physical layer, with TDMA scheduling
- Implemented a new software AM demodulator to improve AM performance in the presence of doppler shift

### Georgia Tech Research Institute | Atlanta, GA

Student Research Assistant

May 2018 — August 2018

Electronic Systems Lab (ELSYS) at GTRI specializes primarily in electronic warfare

- Designed a system convert realtime image data from a backend simulator (OpenEaagles) to API calls for the external frontend program (Prepar3D)
- Created a multithreaded proxy server to exchange UDP data with OpenEaagles and make RPC calls to Prepar3D
- Delivered the functioning system for demonstration after 1 month of work, with an accompanying ICD (interface control document)

### Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, GA

Head Teaching Assistant for Systems and Networks

Teaching Assistant for Systems and Networks

August 2018 — May 2019

January 2018 — May 2018

Intro computer architecture and operating systems course, typically with 250-300 students

- Managed a team of 12 TAs
- Supervised the creation, release, and grading of assignments, including weekly homework assignments and biweekly projects
- Handled the administrative overhead of the course, such as fielding emails from students, and providing and updating course information such as grades and assignment schedules

### Skills and Concentrations

#### **General Concentrations:**

- Embedded software
- Real-time systems and RTOS
- Digital signal Processing (DSP) and embedded transceivers
- · Server backend code
- Physical layer networking
- · Operating systems and device drivers

Languages: Mainly C, C++, also proficient in C#, Java, Python, Matlab/Octave, and client- and server-side Javascript

Familiar Platforms: Linux, Arduino, Raspberry PI, TI C55xx, Native Windows, .NET

**Source Control:** Git. SVN